As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take
in the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled!
La la la la la!
Yeah yeah yeah!
Here we are in between
the sea and the sky.
Ready now for adventure.
We're itching to try!
Get ready to roam!
So all aboard now we're set to go!
Set sail to the ocean so deep!
Ready for a truly grand adventure!
Well don't you think
that sounds really fun!
All this excitement is second to none!
As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take.
In the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled.
La la la la la.
Yeah yeah yeah.
If there's something that
I just won't ever forget.
It's the way that I felt
when our journey was set.
Now I won't be scared.
As long as I keep that feeling there.
With that, let us keep up the pace.
While enjoying every
trip from place to place.
Our timid hearts get the rhythm ingrained.
So let's keep going, adventure awaits!
So many treasures await!
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in
hand, everybody rejoices!
Party on, cause we stand tall and proud!
Life is adventurous, be
aware it's dangerous!
Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
Our master's orders are absolute.
We zombies couldn't oppose
them even if we tried.
But that doesn't affect him at all.
What makes him different?
And wait, why is he as
strong as a general?
My power is one that
is not bound by logic.
It makes the impossible possible.
This unstoppable force that rages like
a hurricane is none other than love.
I'm not exactly sure how this works!
But if he's saying stupid things
like that, that must be Sanji.
You're right.
Hey Sanji, is that really you in there?
Or maybe you're just friends with Sanji?
Either way, he's our friend.
Show your trap, you damn dirty pirate!
Whoa!
I guess that means we're
still his enemy after all.
What's that?
I don't know, but it sounds bad.
Haven't we suffered enough?
Lola, stop!
A one hug in a wedding dress?
Don't be hasty!
Please, listen to your commander, Lola!
Catch me if you can, you little cutie!
What?
You wicked cat burglar!
You'll pay for stealing Master Ab's
greatest treasure! Me? Treasure?
Hold on, I know I'm a pirate and all,
but I haven't stolen anything yet!
You stole his heart!
Now I'm going to tear
yours out of your chest!
You won't lay a hand on this lady!
Shut your mouth!
And get out of my way!
Dogwin! Pin Dog!
That looks bad! Are you okay?
Why didn't he try to fight back?
I already told you,
I'll never kick a woman!
Awesome speech!
Guys, help me!
I'll be taking my bride, thank you!
Now that you can fly!
Some idiots I'm being abducted
here huh by who hey come back we'll
hold the wedding ceremony
immediately all the preparations have
already been made you're that
invisible pervert from the shower
aren't you let me go whoa i guess
it really is invisible huh mommy
i was sizing you up in short i've
determined that you're fit to be my bride
You may call me Absalom.
It's the name of your future
husband, so remember it well.
I don't keep myself in shape so
some sick boy who can drool over me.
So don't treat me like a
piece of meat, you animal!
Thunder Charge!
NAMI!
Great job!
Now keep running!
Don't stop!
We gotta get out of this forest!
What happened?
Even after that, he's still standing up?
That guy is not normal!
Just look at him!
What is this feeling?
Every nerve in my body is dancing!
I'm on fire!
I can feel it coursing through my veins,
as if i've been struck by lightning i see
there can be only one
answer this must be love!
you're not getting away!
we gotta stop staring and start moving!
even if absalom's here it's
still our job to catch them!
you're right and if we fail
perola's going to punish us!
not good at this rate
they're going to hurt her!
i don't know why it is but i feel like i
have to protect that lady no matter what!
why is this body so weak!
i can't even take a single step!
i tell it you guys we gotta catch up!
stop and heed my words!
wild zombies the woman is mine!
don't harm her!
shut up! screw you!
perhaps You can't boss us around.
We only answer to Mistress Perona.
This is out of your jurisdiction.
I said stop, damn it!
I'm not a fool.
I know you're under Perona's command.
But if you have the sense to fear her,
you should know how
frightful I can be as well.
In other words, mind your
tongue when you speak to me.
what the hell do you want i
won't let you touch that lady
hey newbie cut it out man
Absarolm's mad enough already!
Get back here!
Cat burglar!
Hey, Nubby!
I think she's only chasing after you!
You're right!
What the heck is going on here?
Maybe we can just sort of split up!
Are you selling me out,
you heartless bastard?!
Get back here and die already!
Women are scary!
You'll have to run faster than that!
I see.
So that's what happened to them.
I'm warning you, but the
answer spoke on them!
Hear me!
You captured our crewmates, didn't you?
And carried them behind
that wall like a Straw Hat.
Monkey, monkey!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
That's correct.
And just wait!
Because any second now, you'll
be suffering the same fate!
Zombie generals in the front!
Zombie generals behind!
I'd give up if I were you.
Whether you're a dumbass
monkey or a dumbass spider,
it looks like that big sticky web that
caught the sunny when we came here?
was your work, if I'm not mistaken.
In other words, you were
after us from the beginning.
Mistress Perona's ghost network
sees all, knows all, and tells all.
Frankly, you were doomed from the start.
Those big ears of yours must be
useful for gathering information, too.
And you certainly like to run your mouth.
Um, huh?
Sorry, what was that?
You mean they're just for show?
We're completely surrounded.
Worst case scenario, they call it, right?
what we need is a last-second miracle plan
yeah you think I can handle it I'd love to
see you try put on a good show for me you
got it just follow my
lead Check this one out!
Hey! Don't do that!
Here we go!
Kaido!
Oh, crap!
You can't break the friggin' bridge, man!
That's cheating!
What's up?
My plan's super enough for you?
Well, it certainly is violent.
Now, Saul Flu!
Whee!
You...
you can fly?
Yes, for five seconds. Flame!
But actually, that's all we need.
Strong right!
Sweet!
I got the ledge!
That's the building where
they took Straw Hat.
If we can make it up
there, we can save him.
I'm sorry.
I can't hold it.
I'm returned!
A fall like that won't stop a zombie.
But at least they're trapped
in the courtyard for now.
That should buy us some time.
Excellent work, Franky.
Yeah, thanks a lot!
How generous of you to pay a
compliment to your stepping stone!
Now I'm angry.
You are gonna pay for this.
You realize I'm a spider, right?
Give me two seconds and I'll be right up.
Huh?
What is that?
Looks like something's falling up there.
No, someone has fallen.
What do you call a flying skeleton?
I don't know what your
deal is, and I don't care.
She's our friend, and I
won't let you hurt her.
I'm warning you.
I won't stop punching her.
You stop running.
Get away, Nami. Hurry.
The only woman Absalom
has loved to marry is me.
Get off.
Now!
Prepare to die!
Wait!
You've got it all wrong! I...
I'm...
The truth is, I'm a man!
What? What?
Oh, come on.
You...
You mean it?
Yeah, cross-dressing is just a
hobby of mine. I'm not joking.
And, uh,
I think you and that ab guy make a super
cute couple You two
should totally hook it up,
girlfriend What?
You think?
Of course I do.
You were made for each other.
To be completely honest, I
was beginning to lose hope!
All this time?
No one has ever offered me a
single word of encouragement.
You don't know how much it means.
Thank you, thank you!
Raise your head up high, it's okay.
You don't have to thank
me for saying that.
We're friends.
My name is Nami-zo, but
you can call me Nami.
We're friends.
Nami!
She bought that?
Huh? What?
Is that the problem?
I'll put it this way.
If you want to get married, you
can't do it while he's awake.
That's just silly.
You knock him out and get him
to sign while he's sleeping.
Wait, is that really ethical?
I mean, like, as a human being?
Lola, sweetie, you're a zombie.
A loophole!
A rotting zombie loophole!
Remember, if you can't knock him
out, you can always drug him.
Hey, Namizo, weren't we gonna run away?
Oh, by the way, Lola,
I dropped something important back
when I visited the treasure vault.
I'd like to go pick it up,
but I don't remember the way.
Can you give me directions?
Of course!
You big silly.
Just go through Mistress Perona's room.
It's right next door.
Can't miss it.
Wow, Nami, that warthog bought
that hook, line, and sinker.
Be awfully snooty so
nami was a guy all along
no wonder she acts so
manly i swear she treats me
like some sort of beast
hey nami he got up to us
all right then lola this
is your chance to attack
i'll never see him again
and that's perfectly fine
with me there's nothing
stopping you you'll make a
beautiful couple i'll give
it my best thank you for
everything nami you gave
me the courage to Fight!
Excellent!
I'm coming for you!
All right, you two, this is our chance!
A non-violent solution, for us at least.
Wow, Nami, that was awesome!
She's not such a bad girl.
You just have to get to know her a bit.
I know what you're thinking.
I can see it in your eyes!
What kind of stupid
pirate ship doesn't have
any treasure they have
a few chests and such.
But all of them are empty we did pick up
some money they had lying around at least.
What a waste of time
i have to look at your
uncute faces and there's
not even treasure.
I thought this was the
guy who beat crocodile
you'd think he'd have a
bit more to show for it.
Whatever they've got plenty of food
let's take that back with us at least.
Aye-aye!
Mistress Perona!
Hm? Golden?
The Master is calling for a
meeting with the Mysterious Three.
What is that about?
Did something bad happen?
It would appear that Straw Hat
Luffy has just been captured.
This will be the debut of number 900.
Number 900?
For real?
Master Ab!
Get out here and marry me
right now, you big jerk!
You turned invisible and
ditched me again, didn't you?
This is strange.
There shouldn't be any
place left for them to run.
Hey, Kumasi!
Absalom, I mean, Master
Absalom, this is bad.
It seems intruders have...
Hold on, this is important.
Did you see three pirates run past here?
They just disappeared.
Well, actually, that's the thing. Absalom!
What do you want?
I told you I don't like you in my room.
Perona.
Welcome back, Mistress Perona.
Is there anything...
Yeah, I need you to stop talking!
How many times do I have to tell you that?
All right, but just this
once, there's something...
Can it!
Nobody cares!
Don't you think you're being
a bit too strict with Kumasi?
Or rather, way too strict?
He's my underling.
What's it to you?
Anyway, did you hear?
Master is calling for us.
Did something happen?
I suppose you could say that.
Number 900 is making its big debut.
Number 900?
And he must have found a powerful shadow.
I wonder who...
It's a miracle!
They haven't found us yet!
What were you thinking hiding in here?
We were better off before!
What do you want from me?
You were freaking out about that invisible
guy and I found something to climb inside!
How was I supposed to
know it was a zombie, huh?
We'll run away as soon as
we get the chance, okay?
Master Absalom!
That's where you're hiding.
There's something important
I needed to tell you.
Yes?
In addition to the pirates, I'm afraid
that we have another unwanted guest.
Go on, then.
It's him, the humming swordsman.
He's back?
Did someone just fall from the sky?
Hey, is that what I
think it is down there?
It can't be.
Actually, looking at the shape, I
don't think it could be anything else.
Huh?
No!
Hey, hey!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
You think I'm gonna let you get away just
because you broke some measly bridge?
I'm a spider.
I can climb wherever the hell I want.
Monkey, monkey!
You think you can keep
the spider busy for a sec?
What for?
Perfect.
There's an open section right over there.
Anyway, I'm going to
build a spider smasher.
Sticky spider net!
He has a spinneret on his hand.
Time for Zeus fleurs.
Slap.
You slap my eye you awful woman?
No no!
Damn it!
You're playing dirty!
This isn't fair!
Good work, partner!
I'm ready to rock!
Step aside!
My what's that?
This here I just stuck my steel nunchucks
into some stone columns! That's all!
Because when a monster is
this big, you gotta smash him!
Extra high!
Heavy induction!
Where did all that power come from?
There's no way this guy is human!
I said stop it already! Hey!
Sticky spider-nets!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Looks like it's time for ribbons! Nuffins!
Hmph.
Nico Robin!
What the hell are those things?
Mousey, mousey, mouse, mouse!
I was careless. I'm sorry.
I didn't think there'd
be other spiders here.
Damn it!
Serves you right, Tramonkey, Tramonkey!
That's what happens when
you let your guard down.
These guys are my minions.
They're called spider mice.
There's more than 500 of
them here on Thriller Bark.
Once we set our eyes on
you, there's no escape.
We've never once failed
to capture our prey.
From the shadows, from your blind spot,
from where you least expect it, we attack.
And thanks to Dr.
Hunkback's modifications, our
silk webs are unbreakable.
We picked off your friends one by one,
silently carrying them
through the ceiling of the
mansion without anyone
noticing a single thing.
Don't worry about your friends.
As soon as we carry you
off, you'll all be reunited.
Hope you enjoy the ride.
Stop it!
Who the hell is singing that?
Gather up all of the crew!
It's time to ship out Binx's brew.
Sea wind blows to where?
Who knows the waves will be our guide?
Or across the ocean's tide?
Rays of sunshine far and wide.
Birds they sing of cheerful things.
In circles passing by.
My goodness, it looks like you
came to this island after all?
How did you get all the way up here?
I jumped, of course.
I'm quite light.
Since you're here already, I suppose
there's no point in holding back.
Here, I'll tell you everything
I know about this island.
Who are you, huh?
You're not a zombie Does that
mean you're with these pirates?
Hold on, what are you?
Worry not, my friend,
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll put an end to this promptly!
Three verse humming
Arrow not slash
Thank you.